https://www.ukmedix.co.uk/cookies-policy/

Contact
Search for:
Contact
Search for:
Contact
Orange Weekend....
Contact
One a penny, two a penny....
our generics
Cookies & Privacy Policy
At UKMedix Internet Ltd we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. These ‘key points’ summarise some of the more important provisions in our privacy policy. We also recommend that you read the full privacy policy. Information we collectWhen you visit our website, we automatically collect and save your IP address.Where you volunteer this information (i.e. by filling in an online form to use our services), we will also save your name, delivery address, email address, date of birth, telephone number, GP address, patient notes, consultation notes, payment records and details of the medicines you have ordered. Use of your information We use Your Data:To provide our services to you (namely, medical consultations for prescription medications) and to comply with regulatory requirements.To send you details of our goods and services, or those of other companies within our group, but only if you give us permission to do so.We share Your Data:With other third parties where this is necessary to deliver the services.With other business entities within the UKMedix group.With other third parties to send you details of their goods and services, but only if you give us permission to do so. Patient confidentialitySome of the information we collect is medical data. This information is always treated confidentially. We will never disclose medical data unless legally required or permitted to do so. It will not be used by us for marketing purposes unless you give us your express permission. Privacy Policy  – The DetailsUKMedix Internet Ltd (registered number 8805262), whose registered office is at Churston House, Portsmouth Road, Esher, KT10 9AD, United Kingdom (“UKMedix”, we” “us” or “our”) knows that you care how information about you (“Your Data”) is used and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting Your Data.At UKMedix we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our customers and website visitors.This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) forms part of our website terms and conditions (“Website Terms”), as set out here. This Policy explains what happens to any personal information that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site.We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly. Important information about who we areUKMedix is a controller and responsible for all personal data it receives and holds. We have appointed a data protection leader (“DPL”) who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this Policy. If you have any questions about this Policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the DPL using the details set out below:Full name of legal entity:UKMedix Internet LtdName or title of DPL:Thomas O’ConnellEmail address:enquires@ukmedix.co.ukPostal address:UKMedix Internet Ltd, Churston House, Portsmouth Road, Esher, KT10 9AD, United KingdomTelephone number:0203 286 3349 If you have any queries, concerns or complaints about the use of Your Data by us, please raise them with the DPL. If this does not resolve the problem to your satisfaction, or, if you prefer to raise the issue with somebody else, then please speak to Dwayne D’Souza who will deal with your complaint.You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (“ ICO“), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.
Popular Treatments
Viagra
Levitra
Propecia
Priligy
Cialis
Useful Links
How we work
Twitter
UKMedix Pharmacy GPhC 9011005Registered Office:Churston House, Portsmouth Road, Esher, KT10 9ADSuperintendent Pharmacist:Zayd Mahfooth GPhC 2037300
Regulated Service
Popular Treatments
Viagra
Levitra
Propecia
Priligy
Cialis
Useful Links
Twitter
UKMedix Pharmacy GPhC 9011005 Registered Office:Churston House, Portsmouth Road, Esher, KT10 9ADSuperintendent Pharmacist:Zayd Mahfooth GPhC 2037300
Regulated Service
Terms and Conditions  |  Privacy Policy
UKMedix is a registered trademark of UKMedix Internet Limited.UKMedix Internet Limited is a company registered in the United Kingdom.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
×
